* Search for:

[LewRockwell.com](https://www.lewrockwell.com/ "LewRockwell") ANTI-STATE_•_ANTI-WAR_•_PRO-MARKET

Privacy Policy
==============

[Donate](https://donate.lewrockwell.com/products/donations) [\[email protected\]](https://www.lewrockwell.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[](# "Print")

This site is strongly committed to safeguarding visitor’s privacy. It operates under the following strict privacy policy:

The only information we obtain about our visitors is information we need to process credit card charges and fulfill orders for purchases in the store. The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason.

Personally identifiable information provided by visitors (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business.

**Cookies**

Site visitors receive cookies used during online sessions from third party ad and analytics networks for targeting ad content. Cookies are not personally identifiable, and are not required to visit LewRockwell.com

**External Links**

In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third party websites. In no case are visitor information or cookies provided to the third party sites.

However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser.

**Security**

We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-In**

Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives visitors options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications.

**Other**

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to [contact me](https://www.lewrockwell.com/contact/).

#### [Political Theatre](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/)

* [Bolton Demonizes Tulsi Gabbard For Calling Out Ukraine Biolabs: ‘So Bizarre and Off the Planet’](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/bolton-demonizes-tulsi-gabbard-for-calling-out-ukraine-biolabs-so-bizarre-and-off-the-planet/)
* [Jeffrey Sachs Explains the Middle East Policies of Israel/USA](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/jeffrey-sachs-explains-the-middle-east-policies-of-israel-usa/)
* [Steps to Exit the Surveillance State and Protect Yourself Online](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/steps-to-exit-the-surveillance-state-and-protect-yourself-online/)
* [Canada’s Justin Trudeau Fires Back at Trump, Says His Victory Shows ‘Regressive Forces’ Are Taking Over America](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/canadas-justin-trudeau-fires-back-at-trump-says-his-victory-shows-regressive-forces-are-taking-over-america-2/)
* [Canada’s Justin Trudeau Fires Back at Trump, Says His Victory Shows ‘Regressive Forces’ Are Taking Over America](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/canadas-justin-trudeau-fires-back-at-trump-says-his-victory-shows-regressive-forces-are-taking-over-america/)
* [Biden Regime Quietly Extends COVID-19 ‘Emergency Declaration’ to Shield Big Pharma and mRNA Vaccine Makers from Liability Until 2029](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/biden-regime-quietly-extends-covid-19-emergency-declaration-to-shield-big-pharma-and-mrna-vaccine-makers-from-liability-until-2029/)
* [Rep. Thomas Massie Introduces Bill Calling for National Constitutional Carry](https://www.lewrockwell.com/political-theatre/rep-thomas-massie-introduces-bill-calling-for-national-constitutional-carry/)

#### [LRC Blog](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/)

* [How Washington Provoked the New Cold War, with Guest Scott Horton](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/how-washington-provoked-the-new-cold-war-with-guest-scott-horton/)
* [Post-‘Liberation’ Syria Looks A Lot Like Post-‘Liberation’ Libya](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/post-liberation-syria-looks-a-lot-like-post-liberation-libya/)
* [The Neocons and the State of Israel Finally Get Their Regime Change in Syria](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/the-neocons-and-zionists-finally-get-their-regime-change-in-syria/)
* [Robert Barnes and Rich Baris Episode 87: What Are the Odds? Veteran Daniel Penny Acquitted, Potentially Marking an End to the BLM Era. Plus, have Trump’s Nominees Turned a Page?](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/robert-barnes-and-rich-baris-episode-87-what-are-the-odds-veteran-daniel-penny-acquitted-potentially-marking-an-end-to-the-blm-era-plus-have-trumps-nominees-turned-a-page/)
* [Trump Cashes In (Literally) at Picture of Jill Biden Staring at Him . . .](https://www.lewrockwell.com/lrc-blog/trump-cashes-in-literally-at-picture-of-jill-biden-staring-at-him/)

#### [LRC Podcasts](https://www.lewrockwell.com/podcast/)

* Search for:
